Jeff, when I hear you talk about this, I
think of the Tina argument, there is no
alternative. Now, obviously, one answer
is Tina is the answer, there is no
alternative. We'll just basically
continue to do what we're doing even
though it's bad, it doesn't work.
Another answer could be, well, the
crypto bros we're going to work on
making a kind of alternative crypto
system, we'll use stable coins to kind
of bridge from one world to the other.
There's real world financial assets that
are now being tokenized, that's another
potential bridge. But, in some ways, the
cryptoverse is kind of working on this
plumbing. Where do you think we're going
to go? Are we going to try to, you know,
jump from a moving car to another moving
car? Are we going to stay on the
euro-dollar system until something
breaks? Where do you think we're going
in the future?
>> Yeah, I think the first part is true. Uh
what you just said, Ben, is absolutely
true. We're kind of stuck here, and it
is a solution for the short run,
although the short run has turned into
two decades. However, it's not a
workable solution because whenever you
have, the old saying I use is that when
economic growth, the rate of change in
the economy goes down, rate of change in
politics goes up. And the longer the
rate of change in economy stays down,
the faster the rate of change in
politics becomes. In case you haven't
noticed, that's kind of where we are in
the 2020s. So, in many ways, we can't
really stick with the euro-dollar
system, even though we're, you know,
nobody's working on its replacement
specifically. I mean, yes,
some cryptocurrencies fancy themselves
as the reserve currency of the future.
Won't name any names here. The truth of
the matter is, cryptocurrencies, which
should be the natural bridge to the next
next ledger money system, because that's
what the euro-dollar is, it's nothing
more than a in a dispersed ledger, where
the ledger is kept by, you know, banking
banking cartel. There's all sorts of
negatives associated with that alone,
beside the fact that it doesn't work the
way that it did before 2007. I mean,
because the banking sector was the only
way to create this global reserve ledger
system, it allowed the global cartel of
banks that operated enormous political,
financial, way too much power. You don't
want to have that kind of power in the
hands of banks to begin with. Yes, it
was necessary because they were the only
industry available with the resources
and the specialized expertise to pull
off something like this. So yeah, they
were good in the 1950s when we needed
the solution to Triffin's dilemma, which
wasn't really a dilemma cuz they solved
it. So yeah, we needed banks back then,
but you know, we can move beyond banks.
We have the technology in blockchain to
operate ledgers. What we lack is the
expertise to scale them up to to the
size and scale that we need for a global
reserve currency system, as well as make
them robust enough that they can be used
in a reserve currency fashion. So while
there is some potential from
cryptocurrencies and more more so
blockchain, it's still way way down the
road. We're several iterations away from
actually undertaking and equaling the
euro dollar's capacity, let alone
surpassing it. So that's potentially a
future and stable coins are an extension
of the current euro dollar framework
because like you said, Ben, it's
probably best way to put it. They're
tokenizing some real world assets and
financial assets together to put them
into a ledger framework. But in many
ways, that's just kind of a half step
into the future and it not necessarily
doesn't represent it doesn't necessarily
represent a full step into the next
stage of evolution, which I think we
should be moving toward to begin with.
So
in many ways, the cryptocurrency
phenomenon is a response, even though a
lot of cryptocurrency enthusiasts don't
know this, it was a response to the euro
dollar break. I mean, they all think
that they were the Fed's printing money.
We need to we need to protect the value
of the dollar, protect protect the value
of savings. Instead, what they created
was another form of store value
financial asset instead of a workable
currency system, which is what they were
supposed to do. That's where the
cryptocurrency revolution really went.
Even if people didn't realize that's
what they were doing, they were trying
to solve the euro dollar problem without
understanding the euro dollar was the
problem they were trying to solve. And
in many ways, that has hindered their
evolution because they've been looking
in unproductive directions. Like I said,
Bitcoin, perfect example. Bitcoin, the
white paper from Satoshi says a
peer-to-peer payment system. It wasn't
supposed to be a Nasdaq stock, but it
went over to become a Nasdaq stock
because they were thinking they needed
to protect everybody from the Fed's
money printing rather than trying to
work out how to create a euro dollar
alternative, a useful, widely available,
widely acceptable euro dollar
alternative. And there's arguments about
whether or not they could ever do that
with Bitcoin, but that's a separate
thing. So, I think in many ways,
cryptocurrencies took a couple of
unproductive directions, and then
stablecoins kind of brought it back
toward the direction we need to, which
is, you know, a payment system, but
still, like I said, they're couple of
generations away before even coming
close to challenging and recreating what
the euro dollar actually does, even if
it even when it does it poorly.
>> So, Jeff, someone might be listening to
this conversation and say, "Wow, this
guy Jeff's really smart, but I I just
don't get how this matters to me. If the
euro dollar system breaks down in Dubai
or the rest of the world, how does that
affect me? How should I position my
portfolio for some euro dollar shortage
or some dollar issue that I don't really
understand? It doesn't affect my
day-to-day life. What should I be doing
to potentially, you know, guard my
portfolio or guard my wealth from the
things that Jeff's saying?"
>> Yeah, the first argument, the counter
argument along those lines is look at
the stock market, right? You said the
the economy's been in the toilet for 20
years, so how's the stock market at
all-time highs, right? Where there seems
to be a disconnect here. And the answer
to that is the downside isn't
necessarily the stock market having a
bad day or a bad month or a bad year.
The downside is the stock market
continues to soar to new highs as the
socialists take over in city after city
after city, state after state after
state. Because eventually we're talking
about here at the end of the day is an
economy that doesn't function. And the
reason why socialism's become popular is
because the economy that we have today
looks a lot like what Marx warned us
about 150 years ago. It doesn't function
the way it should, therefore it kind of
makes a crazy man in Karl Marx look look
like he knew what he's talking about.
And therefore, you've got everybody on
the other side saying, "Look at the
stock market. Look at how great
everything is. This this system works
really well." And a lot of people, and
there are way too many people who are
struggling saying, "What the hell are
you talking about? This economy sucks
and it has sucked for a very long time.
And here in the 2020s, it seemed to have
somehow gotten even worse." We went from
millennials living in their parents'
basement because there were no jobs to
now those millennials living in their
parents' basement have zero hope, zero
future, and they can't even afford to
live in the basement. So,
the downside here isn't necessarily a
portfolio or the stock market or assets.
The downside is much bigger than that.
It's structural, systemic. We are losing
the system that we have because nobody's
making the argument that we can get out
of the situation that we're in. It's a
two-pronged problem here. The first
problem is we don't have nearly enough
jobs because the economy has been stuck
in depressionary condition cuz the
banking system won't create credit,
won't create money, won't circulate
money. Then for everybody turns into,
rather than risk-takers, which the
economy needs, everybody just plays it
safe, except for the private credit
people who just go off into a bubble
situation. So, it's None of it is
productive. So, we're stuck in this
unproductive loop year after year after
year, decade after decade, which leads
to economic decay. And it's worse around
the rest of the world. Why did we have
the great migrations in the 2010s? Yes,
there were political developments that
came along with it, but the reason why
everybody wanted to move out of the
global south is because suddenly the
future that they thought they were
acquiring in the 1990s and the first
half of the 2000s just simply
disappeared. Where did that go? It just
It's gone. I mean, Brazil was doing well
and some of these emerging markets were
on their way, and then it just kind of
turned off.
So, the issues here are much bigger than
strictly the stock market or portfolios.
Though, I mean, there are absolutely
some uh some spillover there in
financial context, but I The argument
here is much bigger than that. It's It's
the systemic argument. It's politics,
and it goes beyond strictly financial
markets and financial prices. Before we
go on with our video today, let me ask
you a question. What if your gold could
actually pay you every single month in
more gold. That's what today's video
sponsor, Monetary Metals, lets you do.
And here's how it works. You still own
the gold, it's still in your name, it's
fully insured, but instead of just
sitting there doing nothing, it actually
starts working for you. Monetary Metals
has built a system that turns idle gold
into productive gold, earning real yield
paid in physical gold, not dollars. No
selling, no trading, no converting. You
keep your gold and every month you get
more of it. It's a simple idea, but it
solves a big problem. If gold is money,
it should act like money, and now it
finally can.
If you're a long-term gold holder
looking for a smarter way to store
value, check them out at
monetary-metals.com/snyder.
Again, that's
I highly recommend booking a call with
them today to see if they're the right
fit for you. We thank Monetary Metals
for their sponsorship, and now let's get
back to the rest of our video.
>> So Jeff, if someone's listening to this,
wouldn't they say, "Well, wait a minute.
If if the situation is so bad and the US
economy is so broken, and then they face
this kind of untenable system, shouldn't
bond vigilantes show up and say, 'Hey,
it's time to make the US pay their fair
share on these bonds. I don't want 5%
rates or 4% rates. I want junk bond
rates because I'm lending to these guys
who are completely profligate. They've
no idea what they're doing. They have a
broken system,' says Jeff Snyder. So why
are we not seeing bond vigilantes?"
>> Because everything you just cited is a
reason to own safety. And then
unfortunately, the sad thing is, and
this is the one of the most perverse
aspects of the system, we value safety
in government bonds. We see safety in
government bonds. And it's not really
because of the government's fiscal
situation, it's really about liquidity.
It's the fact that government bonds have
the historically the deepest market
associated with them. Now, because bonds
are treated as, you know, reserved for a
whole bunch of reasons, whether they be
statutory or just in practice,
government bonds have attained the
status of being the safest part of it.
And there's I mean some there's
legitimate arguments. I mean, the
Treasury market's most liquid market out
there and in the way the system works,
heavily collateralized, it's really
about safety. So, just like we saw in
the 1930s, I think people missed this
point, too. All the arguments that were
made to that are being made today were
absolutely made in the 1930s. In fact,
Warren Buffett's father made, you know,
the same thing. You know, FDR is
bankrupting the country with his New
Deals spending, which I mean he did.
Treasury market's going to blow up
because deficits before we got to World
War massive deficits that we'd never
seen before. The The '30s deficits were
larger than the Civil War, World War I.
We'd never seen any anything like
peacetime deficits like those. The
federal government's going broke. The
country's in the worst depression in its
economic history. And what did everybody
do with their money? They bought
Treasuries. The yields on Treasuries
kept going lower and lower and lower.
Banks, financial counterparties,
financial participants, nobody wanted to
lend in the real economy just like in
the 2010s, everybody wanted to own what
is perceived of as safety. So, that's
the that's the reason why we don't see
bond vigilantes today is because stuck
in this depressionary circumstance, it's
depression economics, everybody wants to
own safety. And the only people who
don't want to own safety just did a
bunch of stupid garbage that blew up a
huge bubble that's about to blow up in
our face. So, it's it's either one or
the other and neither of those are
really productive uses, like I said. So,
bond vigilantism has been buried
underneath depression economics ever
since 2008. In fact, those two things go
together. It was one of the most
toughest aspects of the 2008 crisis
because you had, you know, under George
Bush, his stupid TARP thing, who
basically broke with all previous
convention after the 1930s and said,
"Give me as much money as I can borrow
or it's going to be the worst case
scenario in human history. He basically
blackmailed the country. Give me TARP,
give me all the funds for TARP. And back
at the time, you know, it was about a
trillion dollars. A trillion dollars was
like, holy crap. This is enormous.
Today, it's a drop in the bucket, but
that's the reason why. Bush said, "Give
me the money for unlimited money from
TARP." A lot of people said, "Uh-oh, the
Treasury market's going to explode, the
dollar's dead." And it was the opposite.
Where we should have had bond
vigilantism, you only had more and more
demand for US Treasuries. And then,
the saddest part of that, the
politicians eventually figured this out.
They had figured out, not necessarily
where this was coming from, but they
figured out, "We have a blank check. We
can borrow an unlimited amount, and it
doesn't seem to matter. There is no bond
vigilantism." The reason we have
deficits that are out of control is
again, because of depression economics.
The politicians realized, "We can create
deficits as as far as the sky can see,
and somewhere there's demand for all of
the debt that we raised in order to pay
for that stuff." And that demand comes
from the depression economics. So, all
the stuff you just said, Ben, are
actually symptoms of the economy and the
system that don't work. And it all goes
back to
the sad history of of prioritizing and
looking at government bonds as as as if
they're safe. And it's really about
liquidity more than safety. That's
really the the original sin here. And
because of that, we're kind of stuck in
this rut, where the bigger government
gets, the worse the problem's going to
be in the economy. That's the Japanese
example to a T. The Japanese did more
and more government finance spending, it
didn't get them anywhere. It It just
left them with huge amounts of debt. It
didn't blow up the yen. It didn't blow
up the currency. It didn't blow up the
bond market. It just left the economy to
suffer from it, because
for all the stuff that Keynes got wrong,
he was right about that. At the end of
the day, when you get into these
depressionary circumstances,
deflationary circumstances, who really
ends up paying for it? Well, the big
guys that created the mess, they get
bailed out. Who ends up paying for the
the crappy depression economy that comes
afterward? It's always the little guys.
Always the workers. So, the worse it
gets for the workers, the more you know
this is the reason why it's there. And
that's why we don't have bond
vigilanteism. There's a reason the
politicians and governments go crazy. No
politician anywhere is going to be able
to sit back and say, "The economy sucks,
which means I need to pull back." Cuz
they'll be immediately criticized for
their austerity. Voting public will go
nuts. There's no political will to
actually restrain governments, which
would actually help the situation.
>> Let's see if I can summarize the Jeff
Snyder thesis, which is that, "Hey, this
euro-dollar system, it started to break
down. And when it did break down in
2008, rather than saying, 'Hey, there's
all this malinvestment in this
euro-dollar ecosystem. Let's flush out
the system. Let's try again. It will be
painful, but we'll figure it out.' We
did the classic moral hazard, which is,
'Hey, let's bail everyone out. Let's
make things super safe.' Of course, the
bond vigilantes died because, 'Hey, we
have this super safe asset, right? We'll
continue to kick the economy along, but
not really fix the problem.' And now
we're in a world where because the
problem doesn't feel like it's fixed,
there's this K-shaped economy, this
broken economy. People feel like, 'Hey,
we got to do something to fix this, but
that something continues to destroy or
reiterate the problem that we've created
before.' Is that why, Jeff, you think
we've seen gold prices continue to rise?
People feel like, 'Hey, I know
something's wrong. I don't understand a
euro-dollar system. The guy, Jeff, is
way too smart for me, but I know there's
something about this economy that isn't
right. And seeing the stock market at
all-time highs doesn't actually fill me
with confidence. It fills me with
confusion. And so, I want to buy an
asset that I know is outside of this
whole financial engineering system.' Is
that why you see gold prices rising in
your view?
>> Yeah, Ben, I think that's probably the
best explanation I've ever heard for
what's going on with gold here. And you
could see it started right at the end of
the 2010s. You know, gold prices started
to rise in 2018, 2019 when people
started You're right. They don't know
anything about the euro-dollar system.
They They don't They couldn't care less
about it. And really, you can understand
where that's coming from. What they know
is this isn't working. This isn't
working and it continues to go on longer
and longer and longer. I don't know what
the real problem is, but I know this is
whatever they keep hearing, it's not it.
The more they say the economy is
booming, the more they say the stock
market is representing the booming
economy, the more I know it's it's just
complete crap. And so what do I want to
do? Where do you I go to protect myself?
This is the reason why gold is, you
know, the age-old the rock that you want
to depend upon in any big storm is
because I think people are extrapolating
ahead and reasonably so and thinking,
"Okay, the system doesn't work, all the
other financial assets are obscenely
valued or at least, you know, not
anchored to anything. If we keep going
in this direction and there is nothing
to suggest that we won't go in this
direction, what's that going to do? It's
going to eventually lead to what we
should have done in 2008 but even more
violent. Like you said, Ben, 2008 we
should have taken our medicine. It would
have been bad, it would have been really
bad, it would have been harmful and ugly
and disastrous and all the any bad words
you can throw out there. It would have
been a catastrophe.
But it would have been much better to
get it done in 2009 than to be talking
about it in 2029 because in 2029, if we
have to do that again and a solution
doesn't arise from the bottom up and
just take over like the Eurodollar did
in 1960, if this continues to go in the
same direction we don't have a solution
for it, it'll be 10 times as messy
because then we're not just talking
about some banks failing and some people
losing their money, then we're talking
about entire systems that are going to
be redrawn and maybe redrawn by some
people we don't want to redraw the
system. So that's where gold is coming
from. Gold is like, "Hey, we don't like
where this is going and nothing suggests
it's going to change. We got to have
something available that at least if it
does get to be that bad, we have some
stability that gets us the bridges to
divide from A to B."
And when we see gold prices continue to
rise, what that says is
more and more people agree with you. You
might have started out pretty lonely in
2018, you know, not many people were
talking about gold then, but it was
pretty long. But nowadays, it's like,
hey,
everybody in China, the Chinese are
saying the same. Why are they buying
gold? Cuz it keeps getting worse and
worse, and nobody provides any answer.
Emerging markets, like I said before, it
seems like in 2008, they just flipped
off the positive future that everybody
thought was coming. Nothing has changed
there. Gold is at the end of every one
of these questions. If you don't really
know what the question is or what the
answer is, that's where gold comes from,
and that's exactly what the demand for
it is. And like I said, the higher gold
goes, the more people agree with that.
>> I want to offer three potential pathways
out. One, of course, is with monetary
metals. People own gold, these financial
ecosystems where you can earn a yield on
gold, you can finance gold production,
this kind of real economy starting with
gold, with gold on financial rails, gold
token payment systems. There's this kind
of gold world, and maybe, you know,
crypto or other real-world assets.
That's one kind of option. Option number
two is that governments say, "Hey,
listen, people are going to wise up and
go, this is not good. We're going to
lose power. So, Jeff Snider, we are
going to do a sovereign wealth fund.
We'll make sure that people have a
portion of this rising stock market. So,
rather than saying, 'Hey, I can't afford
groceries. Why do I care the S&P 500 is
at all-time highs?' They'll say, 'Hey,
it's a good thing the S&P 500 is at
all-time highs cuz I'm getting some
money from that.' We'll look a lot more
like Dubai or Norway than the United
States. Or option number three is that
governments say, 'Hey, listen, we're
here to fix the problem. We know these
crises keep popping up, and we're going
to do more government control." Of these
options, not only, you know, where do
you see us going, but what do you think
needs to happen for all these different
worlds to actually appear?
>> Well, hopefully the last two of those
don't happen because the third one,
obviously, is what we really want to
avoid. And I don't see the second one is
too much different from the third one.
Cuz if you give the US a sovereign
wealth fund, it'll give it the US
government way too much control. And for
as many people who might be in favor of
that idea today, just think about what
it would have been four years ago. How
would that have been used 4 years ago or
5 years ago during the COVID lockdowns?
How much economic and financial power
that would have left in the hands of the
That's a frightful, frightful thought.
What I hope and what I do think is has a
fair chance of succeeding is what you
said in the first option. Not
necessarily strictly with a gold-backed
currency, a modernized gold system, but
a modernized gold system that competes
with other forms of currency. I don't
see any reason why we have to stick with
one form of currency. I think you could
have a government form of currency, you
could have a gold form of currency, you
could have a cryptocurrency, you could
have a reserve cryptocurrency, you could
have a, you know, an algorithmic stable
coin that is backed by nothing. Let them
all go out there and compete because the
marketplace competition will sharpen
everybody's ideas and produce the best
results. And the best results could be
plural. It doesn't necessarily have to
be one or the other. So,
that's not what the government's going
to say. The government's going to say,
"No, no, no, no, we we got our we've got
our currency and that's the one you got
to use." But ultimately, I think this is
one of the biggest points of the
eurodollar system as well as ledger
money overall, the solution comes from
the bottom-up. It's not dictated by
government. The eurodollar By the time
the government's figured out the
eurodollar is even there, it was almost
10 years into the thing. It's actually
probably closer to 15. So, by the time,
you know, the BIS did its study in 1964
and said, "Hey, you know, what? There's
this eurodollar thing out there." It
was, I mean, a decade old by that point.
As long as government doesn't get in the
way and actively try to stifle
innovation like it was doing a couple
years ago, you know, cryptocurrencies
and digital currencies and gold for that
matter, as long as governments don't
stay in the way, there is
experimentation, innovation, as well as
opportunity. The opportunity to replace
the reserve currency system is enormous.
Think about that. What that would mean.
Pioneering a currency that replaces what
we have today across the entire planet.
That would be absolutely enormous. So,
there's a tremendous incentive to do it.
So, I think, given the way history
works, which is bottom-up, eventually,
once we get enough capacity and
technology and expertise, there's got to
be a a level of talent expertise that
goes along with it. Once you get enough
of that, and you guys, by the way, are
leading definitely leading the edge as
far as the gold part of that goes.
That's why I love working with Monetary
Metals. You actually get it.
It's like, "Okay, we get it." So, you
get enough of these people together, and
I think the future looks like we've got
a gold currency, we've got a
cryptocurrency, we've got a you know,
unbacked and people just whatever
currency works best for them, they can
use it. And there are exchanges that
allow you to seamlessly move from one to
the other cuz somebody's figured that
out. It's not going to be perfect
because no monetary system is perfect.
Let's face it, human beings are flawed.
And so, every human system is always
going to go through a boom-bust cycle.
Pretty sure that's the case. We're never
going to be able to regulate the
boom-bust cycle away, but we shouldn't
we should be able to recreate the
prosperity that we enjoyed between the
end of World War II and 2007. That, you
know, approximately 75-year period was
enormously beneficial to human society.
no reason we can't do it again. And if
we do it right, it might be 100 years.
It might be 150 years before we get to
the end of the useful life. And I think
doing it right really is allowing the
bottom-up experimentation to yield the
best ideas, test them in real-world
circumstances so that they are
legitimately robust by the time they're
they get ready for primetime.
>> So, Jeff, would I put you in the there
is no alternative, but there are
alternatives, and let's let a thousand
flowers from currency systems to payment
rails, let those bloom, let the market
kind of create this robustness. Hey, we
have algorithmic coins, oops, those
crashed. Or, hey, we have this system of
an exchange, oops, that's hackable,
right? And over time, this decentralized
system where people say, "Listen, I
don't know how money or currency works,
but I can get 5% on this crypto." Or,
"Oops, I put my money into a crypto that
yielded 2,000% and it blew up." Over
time, we'll get more and more robust
decentralized monetary alternatives.
What do you think are the biggest risks
to that not happening or the biggest
barriers facing those entrepreneurs
today?
>> Uh what you just said, Ben. Because
let's face it, any disruptive technology
doesn't even have to be in the monetary
context. It's anywhere. Uh inevitably
will invite fraud and um mistakes,
right? So, the biggest mistake is
somebody "Oh, I'm going to give you
2,000% on this cryptocurrency. I want
you to use it." And it's it's a fraud,
right? I mean, that's a real risk and
it's a real danger because let's face
it, anything like this is going to
invite all sorts of scams and frauds and
let's face that's that's a lot where the
the cryptocurrency space has gone in
recent years. I think it's cleaned up a
bit in the last shakeout, but still
there's a lot of downside to that.
People get burned too many times, they
start to learn. Again, that's free
market sense competition capital. That's
what it's really about. Capitalism isn't
about money. Capitalism is about
competition. It's somebody who has a
good idea and is able to take that idea
as far as they can. In the monetary
context, that means okay, people get
burned by the 2,000% interest coins that
are just complete scams. They learn not
to go to those. They quickly learn which
ones are legitimate. They go to the gold
back one because hell, that one seems to
be pretty freaking dependable, right?
Maybe there's some downside to use that,
but there's a positive side to use the
other one. So, I'm going to I'm going to
own both forms of currency. I use one
for one thing. See, I think that's the
answer here because we don't really
know. Nobody today can sit here and tell
you what the reserve currency of the
future reserve currencies of the future
really look like. I think that's far
enough into the future and far enough of
away from where we are today that
there's probably some kind of invention
that hasn't been invented yet and it
doesn't have to be a physical object
that will unlock all of this potential.
I mean, you look about the internet and
e-commerce. What is it that made
e-commerce into what actually you know,
the promises of the dot com bubble? If
you remember that you're too young. But
you remember the 1990s, uh e-commerce
was everywhere. E-commerce e-commerce
e-commerce. You could actually visibly
see the potential there. But it didn't
really happen for another, you know, 15
years. And what was it that unlocked
that potential? It was a freaking
smartphone. Nobody knew what a
smartphone was in 1998. But it we took a
smartphone to finally unlock the
potential of e-commerce. So, I think we
can see something similar in, you know,
digital currencies and modern
currencies, where we don't really know
what it is that just kind of puts
everything together. What I think the
positive thing here is that we've got
people who are working on the various
pieces, even if we don't have the way to
arrange them just yet. People are
finally working on the pieces in a such
a way that you can start to see if they
get arranged in exactly the right
fashion, it does lead to the future. The
problem with that is, as we said
earlier, the clock is ticking. The other
side of it is we're stuck in the system
that we have that seems to be unraveling
more and more as we go along. So, we we
need the people over here who are smart
in doing things to get their going
because over here you've got the torches
and pitchforks that are being lit up and
and ready for redrawing the system in
ways that we maybe we don't want. You
can be optimistic about it, which I tend
to be. I think we'll solve the problems
before we get to that part, but you also
need to keep an eye on the other side of
things.